KIAN'S B&B
Should I carry you on my shoulders?
What do we do?
You carry her on your shoulders.
Should I?
SHE GIVES IT A TRY WITHOUT HESITATION
Let's do it.
Look at her posture.
- You have to go lower. Yeah.
- Lower?
- Yeah. Give it a try.
- Wait.
- She says she works out a lot.
- Hold onto me.
- Okay.
Hold on.
- One, two, three.
- It's working.
Come on. Hurry.
- Hurry.
- I got it.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
Three! Okay.
Hey, Zuha!
Hey, be careful.
Wait!
It's open now.
- Let her down.
Hey, Zuha.
- Good job.
- Hey!
Hey, you're strong.
- Hey.
- I didn't think I could do it.
She's unbelievable!
Did you hear her scream?
You did great.
Could you close it for us too?
- Close it too?
- Yeah.
You're so strong.
I'll close it.
You're now good at this too.
I got it.
THEY SUCCESSFULLY CLOSE IT TOO
Nice job.
Zuha.
You can put me
on your shoulders from now on.
I did it.
Yeah, keep it up.
What? It's open again.
THE DOOR HAS OPENED BY ITSELF
That damn door…
THE DAMN DOOR I MADE
One, two…
GRUNTING
MORE GRUNTING
Hey, let me help.
- Pull me.
- One, two, three.
- Okay.
Gosh, that door…
For goodness' sake.
- Should we prepare the ingredients?
- I think so.
LET'S PREPARE DINNER
HE SETS UP THE STOOLS
TAKES OFF HIS SOCKS IN CASE OF A FLOOD
COMPLETELY ADAPTED TO THE KITCHEN
Zuha, it doesn't take long
to make okonomiyaki, right?
- But prepping the ingredients take long?
- It does.
I think cooking might take some time.
Is that so?
- Maybe about seven minutes?
- Really?
Seven minutes per pancake?
All right, let's get started.
My toes…
Zuha said we should prepare the cabbage.
ZUHA, THE PRIDE OF OSAKA JOINS TOO
Is that enough?
- Okay.
- How many servings should we make?
Well, there were eleven of us yesterday.
And two more guests
are coming today, so it's 13.
Then, 14 servings to be safe?
Yeah.
14 PIECES OF OKONOMIYAKI?
It's funny, isn't it?
I find it funny too.
I'm about to lose my mind.
This situation is so funny.
It hits me every once in a while.
WHILE THE EMPLOYEES PREPARE DINNER
FIXES HIS PANTS
GETS READY FOR THE NEW GUESTS
One for a man, one for a woman.
MEANWHILE
Why am I going up the mountain?
I'm almost there.
That must be it.
The red roof.
It looks ordinary from the outside.
"Kian's B&B."
A GUEST IN A BLACK COAT APPROACHES
Snow,
grass fields,
a blue sky,
and Kian's B&B.
KIAN'S B&B
Why does everything look so big?
IT'S BIG FOR REAL
It's so big.
What?
I was so flustered.
I thought,
"How am I supposed to open this?"
"Should I pray?"
There was no one welcoming me.
It was tough.
HELLO, MR. KIAN
I'M AT THE FRONT DOOR RIGHT NOW
ONE MORE GUEST WILL ARRIVE SOON
YOU CAN OPEN THE DOOR TOGETHER
So you need two people to open the door?
I think I can do it by myself.
No, I can't.
Someone's there.
ANOTHER GUEST ARRIVES
Someone's coming.
COMES TO MEET HER HALFWAY
Who's that?
Are you a guest?
Yes, hello.
Welcome. I arrived a little earlier.
Are you a guest too?
Yes, I am.
This is surreal.
Mr. Kian said we need to
work together to open the door.
- Really?
- Yes.
WAITING BY THE DOOR
- But you know what?
- What?
Can I just open it?
Sure.
I think…
Do you know how to open it?
I think I can just open it like this.
If I do this…
SUCCESSFULLY OPENS THE DOOR
- Hello.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Come on in. I'll take that.
- I can clean it with you.
- Sorry?
No, you're a guest.
WELCOMES BY CLEANING THE WHEELS
By the way,
everything's huge here.
It was like Gulliver's Travels.
Huge hangers,
an extremely large TV,
and an extremely large refrigerator.
It was very Kian's B&B-like.
This house is so surreal.
Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Reverend. Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
Come on in.
A PRIEST, NOT A PASTOR
What's your name, sir?
I'm Min Sang-cheon.
- Sang-cheon?
- Yes, Min Sang-cheon.
And your name?
I'm Chae Seul.
- Seul?
- Yes, just Seul.
Just Seul?
- Hello.
GREETING FROM UP TOP WHILE COOKING
I was surprised.
Looking at Kian's B&B
from an art director's perspective,
I found it really interesting
how they didn't make it about snow
just because it was built
in Daegwallyeong.
- Where should I unpack my bags?
- The rooms are…
Actually, there are no rooms.
- The whole place is one room.
- Okay.
You have no privacy in here.
OPEN SPACE WITHOUT PRIVACY
Are there other guests here right now?
They're all out right now.
We have seven other guests at the moment.
- That's a lot.
- Yes.
And two sleep in the living room.
But we need a place to unpack.
- Yes, you need to unpack.
- Yes.
Right now, over there…
Next to the ramyeon box.
That's the only space left.
THE ONLY "PERSONAL SPACE" LEFT
I made a miscalculation.
I didn't expect we'd have so many guests.
AN UNEXPECTED SHORTAGE OF BEDS
Would you like the corner space?
There. It's actually a pretty good spot.
Isn't it taken?
I'm using it, but I can move.
I used it for a day, so I'm sick of it.
I want to sleep somewhere else.
BELOW THE HANGERS
BOSS
CHAE SEUL
- Then, I'll use this space.
- Okay.
NEXT TO RAMYEON BOXES
SANG-CHEON
THE BOSS MOVES AGAIN
Right, my luggage.
My luggage…
BUT THIS SPACE IS…
Then, is she sleeping next to Jun-ho?
Is that a bit weird?
Don't you think so?
It'd be a bit weird, right?
Is a guy using that spot?
- Then, should I go there?
- Then…
- Should we switch?
- Should we?
- Let's switch.
- Sure.
SANG-CHEON AND SEUL SWITCH
Then, the electric heating pad…
Take one of these.
For me? Thank you.
- It's cold at night.
- Thank you.
NEW BEDDINGS PROVIDED
Our spots are settled now.
- They are?
- Yes.
Make yourselves comfortable now.
- Sure.
- Yes.
You can take your time and look around.
Okay.
MEANWHILE, IN THE KITCHEN
We need this for the lotus root.
- We have to grate it?
- Yes.
AFTER WASHING HER HANDS
STARTS GRATING LOTUS ROOT
I'll just slice these right away.
Zuha, it's like this, right?
LONG STRAND
Yes, that looks good.
STARTS CUTTING AFTER HER CONFIRMATION
IN CHARGE OF KNIFE WORK
Is this thin enough for the cabbage?
I think it should be a bit thinner.
- Thinner?
- I think so.
OKAY, THINNER
Or you can just chop those
into smaller pieces.
- Just chop them up more?
- Yes.
Just chop it up.
OKAY, SMALLER
INSTRUCTIONS ON SIZE RECEIVED
A FLURRY OF CHOPPING
Is this a good enough amount?
Yes, that's good.
Really? Okay.
THIS TIME, GREEN ONION
ONE BY ONE, THOROUGHLY
Is this thin enough? Or make it thinner?
It's good enough.
- It is? Okay.
- Yes.
CHOPPING TASK COMPLETE
Right, do we have any sesame oil?
Yes, I bought it.
We should make that.
Cabbage dressed in sesame oil.
Right, salad.
With some sesame seeds.
That salad sounds good, right?
It's delicious.
It's so good. Let's add it to the meal.
- I'll tear them up for the salad.
- Okay.
SESAME OIL
GENEROUSLY
SESAME SEEDS
Did I put in too much oil?
It is supposed to be mild, but…
- Maybe it needs soy sauce?
- Should I add some?
Or some salt? A little bit of salt.
A little bit of salt?
TAKES ZUHA'S ADVICE AND ADDS SALT
I think salt was the answer.
Become delicious.
You know "Moe Moe Kyun"?
Yeah.
MAGIC SPELL THAT MAKES IT YUMMY
THAT'S THE TASTE
- Right? It was salt.
- Yeah.
It's delicious!
It's delicious. It's ready.
CABBAGE SALAD IS DONE
ZUHA LOOKS AT HER PHONE
AND STARTS MAKING THE BATTER
How much is 300 ml of water?
- 300 ml of water?
- Yes.
Isn't that 300 ml?
- Is it?
- I think so.
It's 330 ml.
- Right. You can use that.
- Okay.
My mom sent this to me from Japan.
- Really?
- It's dashi.
Is it Japanese seasoning powder?
Yes.
And the eggs…
A LOT OF EGGS
AND ADDS STARCH
Are you talking with your mom right now?
I'm asking my mom.
KEEPS ASKING HER MOM WHILE COOKING
THE LOTUS ROOT IS TOO BIG
IT'S OKAY
I'M USING IT TOO
I'M MAKING IT TOO
My mom says she's making it right now too.
- Really?
- Yes.
I guess she's really worried.
Of course, she would be.
You're the pride of Osaka.
If you can't make okonomiyaki…
She's teaching her in real time?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
She's so sweet.
Let's cook it.
THE BATTER IS READY
We have three portable stoves now,
so we can make three at a time.
- And it takes seven minutes per pancake.
- Right.
If we make 13, it'll take a while.
AT LEAST 35 MINUTES
Won't the food get all cold?
Or we can cook them in advance
and heat them before we serve them.
- Like pre-cooking them?
- Yeah.
- That's a good idea.
- Right?
We have three pans,
so let's each take one.
- We have three?
- Yeah.
- Take this…
- Okay.
- And put it like this.
Like pancakes. How should I put it?
Pancakes?
LAY DOWN THINLY-SLICED PORK BELLY FIRST
It's cooking fast.
Just… Don't flip it.
Don't flip it?
Don't flip it.
BATTER STRAIGHT ON TOP
WITHOUT FLIPPING PORK BELLY
It's like this.
- Is this right?
- Yes.
Put the lid on
and wait about three minutes.
Gosh, you brought them.
SECRET WEAPON
- Yes.
- Spatulas for flipping.
- It's been three minutes.
- Really?
But will we be able to flip them?
GIVING IT A TRY
Okay.
- In one go?
- Yeah.
- You did it.
- Okay.
It looks good.
Hey, it looks delicious.
YEON-KOUNG'S TRY
I should've waited.
It's good enough.
I was so close.
I'll show you.
Here I go.
You got it. Okay.
That's good enough.
Put it here.
Okay.
THE FIRST BATCH IS DONE
11 PANCAKES LEFT TO MAKE NOW
Jun-ho, I'm tired.
Let's change bedtime to 10:00 p.m.
I think we'll end up
going to bed later tonight.
We can't.
They'll stay up on their last night.
No, lights-out is at 11:00 p.m.
I don't think it will be.
What are you talking about?
It's 11:00 p.m. That's the rule.
You can't change it like that.
So what should we call you? Kian?
- Or Mr. Kian?
- Me?
- Whatever you like.
- Whatever?
- Let's go with Mr. Kian.
- That seems best.
"Mr. Kian"? A bit formal, but okay.
- Then, Kian.
- Then, we'll call you Kian.
I just said whatever you like,
and then you made things awkward.
Then, Reverend, are you…
No, I'm a priest.
I'm so sorry.
You're a priest. Got it.
Both believe in Jesus, but…
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
I'm a Buddhist, so…
Well, I noticed you were wearing
a rosary on your wrist.
It's all right. It's no problem at all.
What brought you here?
Well, I didn't really have the time
to go traveling.
- Right.
- When I turned 20,
I entered a Catholic seminary
to become a priest.
- When you were 20?
- Yes, in college.
I went to a Catholic school
right after high school.
I received training for ten years.
During the semester, I lived in the dorms.
During vacations,
we'd go back to our hometowns.
But I always had to work
in the church I belonged to,
so I didn't have time to go trips.
But after becoming a priest,
I can take days off now.
And I've realized how fun trips are.
As a priest, you don't have
many chances to go on a trip
with regular people
and get to know them.
Not only was it a challenge
but also a dream for me.
- Anyway, I'm not here as a priest.
- Right.
I'm here as a guest and traveler.
As a guest?
Are you religious?
I'm not.
You're not?
You should pick a faith before you go.
You see,
one of the guests is a monk.
Is he here right now?
He went to the temple.
HE'S HERE NOW
KNOCK, KNOCK
Knock, knock.
Yes?
Could you open the door?
Sure.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Hello, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Are you a priest?
- Yes, I am.
I see. Hello.
Are you a monk?
No, I'm not a full-fledged one.
- I see. Hello.
- Hello.
This is a connection,
as Buddhism would say.
Thank you.
AFTER GUEST JUN-HO RETURNS
THE FRESHMEN RETURN TOO
- They're here.
- There they are.
- Someone's here. It's a priest.
- It's a priest.
- Hello.
What's up?
THE TWINS ARE BACK TOO
- Do you need help? Hello.
- Hello.
Are you twins?
- Yes.
- Did you have a good trip?
- Yes, I did.
Most of them are here.
TOTAL 9 GUESTS ON DAY 2
Geez…
- Hi, Boss.
- Hey.
Come on in.
- You've made a lot.
- Yes.
Thank you.
After we come back,
we can just heat these up
when we grill the meat.
What time is it?
Sunset is at 6:30 p.m.,
so we have an hour.
- Let's go now.
- We should go now.
It's either ice sledding or fishing.
So which one?
Or they can do whichever one they want.
Let's ask them.
Hey, everyone.
Before the sun sets,
and since the lake is frozen right now,
we can go fishing
or ice sledding.
So…
Does anyone want to go fishing?
Me.
Ice sledding?
Ice sledding.
Then, you lead those
who want to go ice sledding.
Okay. Bundle up.
Let's go.
LAKE, KIAN'S B&B
THEY ALL GO TO PLAY ON THE ICE
ICE SLEDDING
Sledding.
Watch your step.
You went running in the morning too.
Aren't you tired?
No, I'm totally fine.
I wanted to do this today as well,
so I'm really excited.
That's good.
It's frozen solid.
THEY REACH THE FROZEN LAKE
Oh, my gosh.
- This is amazing.
- Yeah.
A BIG LAKE NEAR KIAN'S B&B
THE BOSS FOUND IT WHEN HE FIRST VISITED
Is it okay to do ice fishing?
Yes, they said it's okay.
It must be really deep in the middle.
About 40 m?
That sounds about right.
HE TASTES THE WATER
What should we do here?
When I saw it,
I wanted to fish
while looking at the scenery
and go sledding.
Here, the guests can enjoy
a different kind of experience outside.
That's why I planned it this way.
THE FLOWING LAKE
IS FROZEN SOLID NOW
A SNOW-WHITE PLAYGROUND
I wouldn't have known this was a lake.
- It just looks like frozen land.
- Right?
This is incredible!
- It's so cool here.
- I know.
Come, and each take one.
YEON-KOUNG IS IN CHARGE OF ICE SLEDDING
Two holes should be enough.
BOSS IS IN CHARGE OF FISHING
Here, take this.
FISHING TEAM, SLEDDING TEAM
This way for fishing.
EXCITED
There we go. Gosh, the water.
FISHING HOLE OPENED
- Two people per hole.
- Okay.
- Sounds good.
- Here?
ONE MORE HOLE FOR THE TWINS
AMAZED
The ice is thick.
THE ICE IS ABOUT 30 CM THICK
SHALL WE GET STARTED?
Hold on, why does it keep doing this?
- How do you do this?
- What?
Is this your first time fishing?
- Yes.
- It is?
Take this and… Look.
Don't unwind it all.
MR. KIAN'S FISHING CLASS
Take an earthworm.
Is it alive?
There. I put it to sleep.
I'm sorry.
HOW TO ICE FISH
1. PUT BAIT TO SLEEP
Now, bait the hook.
2. STICK ON THE BAIT WELL
Stick it on.
Bait the hook. Now, look.
Put it in the water.
Take the rod, and do this.
3. LURE FISH WITH MOVEMENT
Up and down.
If a fish bites it, you'll feel it.
- Okay.
- When that happens, just pull.
4. TIME IT RIGHT AND PULL
You baited the hook? Nice.
CHAE SEUL HAS EXPERIENCE
But are there fish in the water?
Yes. Apparently, there are masu salmon.
SMELT AND MASU SALMON LIVE HERE
How long does it usually take?
Sometimes, you catch something right away.
Sometimes, you don't catch anything
for three days.
For three days?
Or four days.
Just relax and enjoy the scenery too.
It's exciting when your hands
feel a fish on the line.
My hands?
OKAY, GOT IT
Come to us.
It's no fun if we don't catch anything.
We need to get a nibble at least.
Everyone, hurry up and get on.
- Two more.
- Two?
MEANWHILE, SLEDDING TEAM
Is that how you ride it?
Should we get on our knees?
GRUNTING
It goes pretty smoothly.
THE SPIRIT OF A 20-YEAR-OLD
POWERING THROUGH
Let's go.
JUN-HO PUSHES YEON-KOUNG
This is fun!
- Sit tight.
- Okay.
Thank you!
I never imagined this day would come.
My gosh!
Should we have a race or something?
A race?
A contest?
- Are we doing a race?
- Count me in!
A RACE? COUNT ME IN!
- Should I join too?
- You four.
Hey, don't cross the line.
Up to here, right?
No, you can't.
Okay, are you ready?
KIAN'S B&B'S SLEDDING RACE
Ready.
Get set, go!
Go!
YEON-KOUNG
No, wait!
Hey, this is like the Winter Olympics.
COMPETITIVE SPIRIT
I'm going to win the gold medal.
COMPETITIVE YEON-KOUNG TAKES THE LEAD
She's catching up!
ZUHA'S SURGING AHEAD?
CLENCHING HER TEETH
- She's catching up!
- I won!
YEON-KOUNG, 1ST PLACE
- First place!
- She won!
- The winner!
SO CLOSE
PANTING
One more.
Gosh, I'm not good at this.
MEN'S DIVISION MATCH
- Hold on.
- Here. This is the line.
STRICT
Someone signal the start.
Zuha will do it.
AHEM
She's suddenly clearing her throat.
Ready!
Get set, go!
No way!
TRYING HARD
- Hey, Lee Jun-ho!
- Lee Jun-ho!
JUN-HO
Lee Jun-ho!
- First, second, third, fourth, fifth.
- Goal!
OVERWHELMING VICTORY
NICE JOB, JUN-HO
He's the winner.
- I got the gold medal.
- Nice job.
- Lee Jun-ho!
BOISTEROUS
Goal!
They're so noisy. We're fishing here.
They're quite annoying, aren't they?
ANNOYING?
- They're bothering us.
- Right.
Do they own the place or something?
What's going on?
Come on out.
STUDYING THEIR FACES
Geez.
RESTLESS AND WORRIED
What does it feel like
when something bites?
You'll know it when a fish bites.
Once we catch something,
we'll have way more fun than them.
Really?
It's crazy.
You'll want to go fishing every day.
WANTING THEM TO EXPERIENCE IT
I feel some kind of movement.
Nibbles. He said we'd feel nibbles.
THE NIBBLES HE MENTIONED?
FINALLY A BITE?
I think it brushed by.
What?
THIS FEELING!
NOTHING BUT THE BAIT
Darn it.
DISAPPOINTED
Maybe they're hibernating.
You're supposed to do this
while listening to quiet sounds of nature.
We have such quiet sounds of nature today.
VERY QUIET SOUNDS OF NATURE
Lee Jun-ho!
Kim Yeon-koung!
IN DIFFERENT WORLDS
Why do I feel so angry?
It's annoying enough to not get any bites.
GLANCING
Smita's turned her back.
LOSS OF INTEREST
I bet this is her last time fishing.
- Her first and last.
- Yeah.
Most people never do it again
when their first time goes like this.
- Do you want to do that?
- Sorry?
You don't have to do this.
You can join them.
- We're okay.
- Really?
- Yes.
- All right.
We are okay.
You all look lonely here.
- Keep it down, will you?
- Yeah.
All the fish are running away.
TAKING IT OUT ON HIM
They're running away?
Yes, because you're being so noisy.
Should we stop?
Have you given up?
- What?
- Have you given up?
No, not giving up.
We're just wrapping it up beautifully.
- It was fun.
- It's nice that we didn't kill anything.
Right, let's wrap it up beautifully.
I'd never been
on the ice like that before in my life.
It was such a nice experience.
After going fishing,
that was our first and last time.
That's it.
Let's go!
It felt like a dream.
I'd never tried it before,
so it was even better.
I looked at the distant mountains
as I rode the sled,
and the sun was setting.
It was so romantic.
THE DEFINITION OF ROMANTIC
- Let's put away the things we brought.
- Okay.
Okay, let's wrap it up.
That was so much fun.
We picked the wrong fishing spot.
I bet the food's getting cold.
LET'S GO EAT
Let's grill some meat.
Damn it.
BACK TO PREPARING DINNER
Tonight is your last night?
- It's tomorrow night.
- Tomorrow?
- That's good.
- It is?
It's good that we're leaving?
No, it's good
that tonight isn't your last night.
FLUSTERED
Hey, why are you getting offended?
You said that was good.
Yes, it's good
that you're here one more day.
- Okay.
- Because it would've been a shame.
- You're not that bad.
Do you want an Indian name?
Give me one.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I have one for you.
What is it?
Sukhwinder.
Skowinde?
Skwindle?
- Sukh…
- …winder.
Sukhwinder.
- Yes.
- What does it mean?
What does it mean? It means…
A person who fights.
But that's too cool for me.
- No, really.
- I'm honestly not that manly.
I'm pretty feminine.
- Really?
- Yes, feminine.
FEMININE BOSS
I have a bit of a feminine side.
You do.
Yeah, as I get older…
FEMININE WARRIOR
Is rice okay?
I'm glad you're here.
After I put rice on the trays,
you can put this.
Got it.
IN CHARGE OF SERVING THE FOOD
KIAN AND JUN-HO
IN CHARGE OF OKONOMIYAKI
ZUHA
It does smell like okonomiyaki.
IN CHARGE OF GRILLING
YEON-KOUNG
I like them crisp.
Can I grill them that way?
Of course.
THE MEAT IS READY TOO
Excuse me, could you help me out?
Okay.
Everyone, come take your food.
Thank you.
If you need more,
we'll bring some more down.
They grilled a lot of meat.
CABBAGE SALAD, PORK BELLY, OKONOMIYAKI
PLENTY OF EXTRA FOOD
This is a lot.
Okay, come and sit.
- Take your seats.
- You can sit wherever you want.
We always end up like this.
SITTING IN A CIRCLE
- We're wrapping up the day.
- Right.
- Tell them about your okonomiyaki.
- Yeah.
My okonomiyaki?
What should I say?
It's a famous dish from Osaka.
- It's Osaka-style, right?
- Right.
I wanted to try making it,
so I learned it from my mom in Japan.
But I'm not sure about the taste.
- It'll be good.
- Please try some.
Please enjoy.
- Thank you!
Thank you for the food.
It felt like I was being judged,
so I was nervous.
It's really good.
It's so good.
It's better than what I had in Osaka.
You're a good cook.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That's a relief.
It's good.
So you came here and got ready
before the first guests arrived?
Yes.
After we had lunch yesterday,
that's when we started getting calls.
We never knew so many would come.
Right.
We did think more would come today.
SANG-CHEON AND CHAE SEUL
3 DAYS, 2 NIGHTS
And the two of you came.
The amount was perfect.
You're right.
Ms. Kazuha, it's delicious.
- Thank you.
- I'm glad.
Let's go up. We need to do the dishes.
Gosh, doing the dishes all day.
Doing the dishes all day.
You'll do the dishes?
Yeah.
LET'S DO THEM TOGETHER
LAUGHING
They're having a blast.
I'm glad.
- Mr. Sang-cheon?
- Yes?
You said you'd visit a temple tomorrow?
Yes, I wanted to visit one.
- Naksansa Temple?
- Yes.
- Let's go together.
- Sure.
You could show me around
since I don't know much about it.
I can be your guide.
We're friends.
- You're the same age?
- Yes.
- The same age.
- I see.
BOTH BORN IN 1989
Catholic and Buddhist.
And I'm a half monk.
Wait.
There's that meme.
Before every game, you do this.
I think I've seen it.
- "Lord, I'm sending someone up there."
- Right, on IG.
It's like…
"God Yeon-koung."
"Lord, I'm sending someone up there."
It's so cool.
If we get hit by your spike,
we'd die, right?
Come on.
- Who wants to get hit?
- Jae-eun.
Clench your teeth.
"Clench your teeth."
Would people like me in India?
Totally.
- Would I do okay?
- You're the best.
Should I enter the Indian market?
You're so funny.
Should I teach you an Indian dance?
- Dance?
- An Indian dance.
Isn't it something like this?
No, that's not it!
She said it wasn't.
You should learn it properly.
CAN'T HELP BUT GET UP
- Show us.
- How do you do it?
At weddings,
you dance like this.
What?
- Many people do this.
- Really?
- There's a difference.
- You're good.
There's definitely a difference.
What else?
I think my knees would give out.
You try it.
Like this.
You're so flexible.
UNTIL THEY CAN DO IT RIGHT
I want to pitch a tent
Give and take back.
Give and take back. Then, give it to them.
Like this.
YES, THIS IS SO FUN!
They're loving it.
They're having fun.
LET'S HAVE FUN TOGETHER
Pitch a tent
Give and…
Give and take back.
- It's good to see them have fun.
- It is.
It turns out Yeon-koung
is actually really good with guests.
- Right, she's good.
- Yeah.
I'm not a good talker, so…
She doesn't let them get bored.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
You're really doing it at midnight?
You have to celebrate
birthdays at midnight.
That's in four hours.
THIS MORNING
There's nothing we need
at the market today.
- For Yeon-koung.
- What?
- Seaweed soup for Yeon-koung.
- It's today?
It's tomorrow.
TOMORROW'S HER BIRTHDAY
It's actually tomorrow.
So we should do it at midnight.
THEY PLAN HER BIRTHDAY PARTY FOR MIDNIGHT
At midnight,
it'll be Yeon-koung's birthday.
- Right.
- You know, right?
And I don't think we can get a cake.
So you know how people
build cakes with choco pies?
You can do it, right?
THEY'LL PREPARE A CHOCO PIE CAKE
First, I need to buy…
BUYING THINGS FOR THE PARTY
HE PICKS THE SEAWEED CAREFULLY
Where's the Mon Cher?
Where do I buy candles?
WHILE THEY WERE EATING
HIDES THE CANDLES AND GIFT
BEHIND HIS SLEEPING AREA
PUTS ASIDE SNACKS FOR THE CAKE
OPERATION BIRTHDAY PARTY
Wait until midnight?
- I'll try to stay awake.
- Of course.
YEON-KOUNG GOES TO SHOWER WITHOUT ANY CLUE
Now that I've showered,
I feel it.
- You feel tired?
- Yeah.
Today's the day.
HAPPENS TO BE VERY TIRED TODAY
I'll sleep well tonight.
9:00 P.M.
3 HOURS BEFORE YEON-KOUNG'S BIRTHDAY
Everyone, have a drink.
I'll go take a quick shower.
- Want to wash up? Go ahead.
- Yes.
EMPLOYEES LEAVE TO WASH UP
- Cheers.
- Welcome.
Welcome, you two.
So, how do you like it here now?
When I first arrived,
I just thought it looked simple
from the outside.
But as I got closer,
it slowly grew bigger.
So as expected,
I knew it wouldn't be that simple.
I thought it was so creative.
And this is such a rare experience for us.
Right.
RUMMAGING
So…
What's that?
- What's that?
- Well…
I bought some things for you all.
First, this is for the B&B staff.
- One for each of us?
- Yes.
I got something for everyone.
HE VISITED A SOUVENIR STORE
They have a lot of good stuff here.
Since it's the New Year…
BOUGHT KEYCHAINS THAT WARD OFF BAD LUCK
Since he's "84," the Year of the Rat.
- Thank you.
- This is so touching!
- The Year of the Rat.
- That's right.
- Mr. Kian, the Year of the Rat.
- Thank you.
- The Year of the Dragon.
- Yes, that's me.
Thank you.
Kazuha, the Year of the Sheep.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Of course.
- Don-hee.
Gosh, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
It's cute.
I bought these
in the hope that all of you
and Kian's B&B will prosper.
I wish you happiness too, Jun-ho.
Thank you.
I can't believe
you bought one for each of us.
There's a reason
why I shared such nice things.
It's because it's my birthday today.
Really?
I wanted to share
this good feeling with all of you.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Happy birthday. But…
VERY FLUSTERED
- Is it the 25th?
- Yes.
HER BIRTHDAY IS THE 26TH
Gosh, we had no idea.
ONLY PREPARED FOR YEON-KOUNG'S BIRTHDAY
Hey, let's add a candle here.
What should we put there?
- A candle.
- Yeah, let's do it.
Wait, we don't have any candles?
No, we don't have any.
Hold on a second. Candles…
BIRTHDAY CANDLES?
EXCHANGING LOOKS
Candles?
CANDLES HE BOUGHT EARLIER FOR YEON-KOUNG
FIDDLING WITH THEM
Just in case someone had a birthday,
I brought a candle.
Oh, my gosh!
YOU HAVE A CANDLE?
It was just in case
someone had a birthday.
I brought one.
You carry such things around?
It's just in case.
KEEPS SAYING "JUST IN CASE"
- He has it all.
- He's perfect.
PERFECT GUY JUN-HO
Why didn't I think of that?
- Just in case.
- I could've been a perfect guy.
Jun-ho lights Jun-ho's birthday candle.
- One, two, three.
- Happy Birthday to you
- Happy Birthday, dear Jun-ho
Wait!
- Make a wish.
- Right, a wish.
I wish for everyone's happiness.
What a beautiful night.
This is amazing.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Thank you. I wish you all well.
10:00 P.M.
2 HOURS BEFORE YEON-KOUNG'S BIRTHDAY
So, shall we get started then?
We should open it tonight.
THE KARAOKE ROOM OPENS SOON
Everyone, are you ready?
Yes!
All right.
HE PUSHES THE BUTTON
And when it turns into a stage,
disco ball lights will come out
of the wedding ducks' eyes.
Sparkle, sparkle.
ORDINARY WEDDING DUCKS
WHEN THE KARAOKE ROOM OPENS
The wedding ducks' eyes spin around
as the disco ball lights turn on.
I thought,
"I knew he wouldn't let us down."
"How bizarre."
This is insane!
KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE
Mr. Kian is here!
Boss!
Let's go, Boss.
It's really like we're watching a huge TV.
Hello.
I thank all of you
for coming such a long way.
I thought Season 2
of Kian's B&B would never happen.
But here we are.
And so, I'm very moved and grateful.
Thank you!
So, in the hopes
of having you rest comfortably,
as if you were at a friend's house,
we built this house.
Now, shall we sing some songs?
- Yes!
HEE-JEONG AND JAE-EUN GO FIRST
Hee-jeong, you can go that way.
You can climb up the ramyeon boxes.
I think I'm good.
- She sure is strong.
- I'm okay.
Gosh, she climbed up so easily.
Hey, it's about to open!
Make some noise!
WHAT WILL BE THE FIRST SONG
OF KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE ROOM?
I saw the title.
I can tell just from the intro.
"MY HOUSE"
BY 2PM
I can't watch this.
It's alright, let's go to my house
It's alright, just make it secret
Everyone, what?
In 10 minutes, I'll be waiting
For you over there
- Let's go to my house
- A round of applause!
- Okay.
Okay, keep singing.
Okay! He's coming up.
Okay, let's go!
Here comes Jun-ho!
Come with me
Let's get out of this noisy place
Without anyone knowing
No bad intentions
Just wanna know you more
He's really coming!
Hold on!
It's alright, let's go to my house
Lee Jun-ho!
It's alright, just make it secret
Sing it!
In 10 minutes, I'll be waiting
For you over there
- It's alright, let's go to my house
- It's alright, let's go to Kian's B&B
Okay!
It's alright, let's go to Kian's B&B
Lee Jun-ho!
It's alright, just make it secret
- You're so cool, Lee Jun-ho!
- You look so cool!
In 10 minutes, I'll be waiting
For you over there
It's alright, let's go to Kian's B&B
Let's go!
Thank you.
Great song choice.
It was an honor.
- Great choice.
- It was an honor.
- Thank you.
- You picked the perfect song.
Next song.
Hey, Jun-ho.
Real singers sure are different.
They picked the perfect song.
- I thought so too.
- Very good.
Hey, high five. You were so cool.
- Thank you.
- You were good.
But for real, it's not easy to go first.
Our screaming suddenly gave way
to beautiful singing.
When he showed up, I was so surprised.
- I did it thanks to you.
- Thank you.
You sang my song, so I was able to do it.
I think Jeong-won and Don-hee
might be trembling in there.
There's no way around it.
Let's just do it.
THE VERY NERVOUS SECOND TEAM
We'll end up dancing silly anyway.
They might think
not knowing the song is charming too.
Right.
If they have any sense of humor,
they should do "SPAGHETTI."
LE SSERAFIM'S SONG, "SPAGHETTI"
They should do "SPAGHETTI."
"SPAGHETTI" should be next here.
1 HOUR AND 30 MINUTES BEFORE HER BIRTHDAY
The next song!
We're sorry.
We don't know it very well.
"SPAGHETTI"
BY LE SSERAFIM
Oh, no.
It's your go-to meal
- Now you're a regular
- And fall in love
Can't get enough of that taste
We're in the kitchen
Hey, it's a complete mess.
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
Do you know the dance?
Just a little.
Let's go!
SPAGHETTI SQUAD TO THE RESCUE
Completely melts
You're coming up?
I'm going to step on this.
THE CHORUS IS APPROACHING
THE CHORUS BEGINS
Slowly, now.
It's going to end!
IN A RUSH
- Oh, no.
- The chorus is going to end!
THE SPAGHETTI SQUAD JOINS THEM
Just give up, you know you will
Hey, you guys! Move to the side!
Kazuha!
It's LE SSERAFIM!
Completely melts in your mouth
Hey, get ready!
THEY ARE
READY
Stuck between your teeth, that's SPAGHETTI
Wanna get it out? Bon appétit
Just give up, you know you will
Stuck in your mind, that's SSERAFIM
HE'S ON THE PHONE
Nice job!
THE 2ND ACT ENDS
It's for the next performance.
It's nice that it closes.
- That was tough.
- Good job.
Good job, everyone.
Good job.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. It was an honor.
- Not at all.
- Seriously.
I'll never forget every moment of it.
I loved every second of it.
Now, we have to listen to Kian sing one.
BOSS'S TURN
Let's go!
Please sing a good song for us.
He said he'd sing a slow song.
Then, the mood will be…
He said he wanted
to show off his singing skills.
Mr. Kian is here!
To wish you all tremendous success…
and recognition in the future,
I will sing this song!
"HEEJAE"
BY SUNG SI-KYUNG
- "Heejae."
- It's a great song.
I won't skip the intro!
I'll sing without skipping the intro!
Why is he dancing to a slow song?
How adorable.
Like an old man.
He's trying to hide
his awkwardness with his whole body.
The sunlight falls for us
And the wind made us caress each other
Amidst our laughter
The seasons came and went
You look cool!
- You're so handsome!
Just how much I loved you
And just how much I cried
My love
Please don't forget for even a moment
Remember me
And wait for me
In the place you've gone to
Looking good!
I'll be here getting closer to you
Day by day
We love you, Boss!
You're so handsome, Oppa!
- You're so cool, Oppa!
I love you.
- We love you!
- Oppa!
You look handsome, Oppa!
Something must be wrong with my eyes!
BOSS'S PERFORMANCE ENDS IN GREAT SUCCESS
You were so cool.
Okay, it's 11:00 p.m. now.
1 HOUR BEFORE YEON-KOUNG'S BIRTHDAY
SHOCKED
- What? No.
- No.
But it's 11:00 p.m.
- But it's 11:00 p.m.
NICE JOB, TWINS
- Kim Yeon-koung!
You…
POINTING FINGERS
AFFECTIONATELY AT EACH OTHER
How could you do this to me?
Please sing for us.
The volleyball goddess!
But it's 11:00 p.m. now.
BUT IT'S BEDTIME…
- I know.
- Is lights-out at midnight today?
Let's do that.
NERVOUSLY WATCHING THEM
Some didn't get to sing,
so let's make it midnight.
- Keep going?
- Yeah.
- To the end?
- Yeah, it's their last night.
FRESHMEN CHECK OUT TOMORROW
Okay, until 12:00 a.m.!
LIGHTS-OUT AT MIDNIGHT CONFIRMED
Okay, it's God Yeon-koung's turn.
- Open already?
- She opens it right away.
Okay, let's have fun together.
- Okay!
Are you ready?
- Yes!
Get ready!
"YOU IN VAGUE MEMORY"
BY HYUN JIN-YOUNG
Bam!
Let's go!
Jump!
A DANCING MACHINE APPEARS
You turned away from me
From me!
You walked away from me
Kim Yeon-koung!
I want to fold it away
Into my precious memories
As time flies by
I can't find…
- Myself!
Everyone.
- Yes?
Before you leave, I hope you all have fun
and make great memories. Thank you.
Thank you.
To our Kian's B&B, let's go!
- Let's go!
- Kian's B&B.
Thank you so much.
- That was insane.
This was pretty hard.
Good job, everyone.
Thank you so much.
- Good job, everyone.
- Great job.
Everyone.
You were great.
- Thank you.
- You were great.
Thank you for cheering me on.
MEANWHILE
- What time is it?
- What?
Should we do it exactly at 12:00 a.m.?
But she might go to bed before then.
No, she won't. Never.
Then, in that case…
I'll sing a song at around 12:00 a.m.
Together?
Together. And should we do
the cake up there?
- She won't see it.
- Right.
She won't be able to see the cake.
Let's do it here.
THE MEETING CONTINUES RIGHT NEXT TO HER
I'll go up and put it
next to the fireman's pole.
- Okay.
- We'll come from over there.
- Then, you go up and stand by.
- Right. Okay.
Zuha and I will bring it.
Okay.
ACTING AS IF NOTHING'S GOING ON
OPERATION BIRTHDAY PARTY
KIAN DISTRACTS HER WITH SINGING
JUN-HO AND ZUHA
BRING THE CAKE TO SURPRISE HER
11:15 P.M.
45 MINUTES BEFORE YEON-KOUNG'S BIRTHDAY
WORRIED YEON-KOUNG MIGHT GO TO BED
If you didn't sing yet, get ready!
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Let's go, twins!
- Let's go!
THANK YOU, TWINS
Look at their dance.
All right!
They've definitely done this before.
Can I sing a slow song?
35 MINUTES BEFORE BIRTHDAY
Sounds good.
NICE, GUEST JUN-HO
Whatever you like.
That wig is so funny.
It keeps shaking.
He looks like the sheep we saw today.
Everyone, you each need
to have a song in mind.
- Is a hymn okay?
- That's okay too.
HELP US, FATHER
A gospel song's okay too.
A slow song is okay too?
- Of course.
- It's okay if it's not upbeat?
AMEN, FATHER
IMMERSED
Listen to the lyrics, Jeong-won.
- Okay.
- They hit home.
Got it.
It's so good.
RELIEVED
All right, who's next?
- Who's next?
- One more person?
- Okay, a singer. Okay.
Can you two sing one more song?
SINGING AGAIN?
JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER
You can sing more songs if you want.
We'll end at 1:00 a.m. at this rate.
Let's sleep in tomorrow.
FLUSTERED
- Let's sleep in.
- We can just send the address to people.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Is that okay?
And what I really want is for them
to come in by themselves,
have fun, and go on their way.
That was random.
I mean, we're too…
Close-minded?
We need to think
outside the box right now.
AN IMPASSIONED SPEECH TO STALL FOR TIME
We really should.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- So just let them come tomorrow?
- Yes.
Over the phone?
WHILE THE KARAOKE ROOM FUN CONTINUES
11:55 P.M.
5 MINUTES BEFORE YEON-KOUNG'S BIRTHDAY
JUN-HO CHECKS THE TIME
HE GOES TO PREPARE THE PARTY AS PLANNED
HE SECURES THE PRESENT
SPACING OUT WITHOUT ANY IDEA
THE HIDDEN SNACKS TO SERVE AS THE CAKE
GLANCES DOWNSTAIRS
TALKING WITH GUEST JUN-HO
- Not bad, right?
- It's the most important.
Really?
I GOT THE THINGS FOR THE CAKE
ZUHA, COME TO THE DOOR
AFTER SHE GETS THE MESSAGE
I'LL BRING OVER WHAT I BROUGHT
SHE RUNS OVER HOLDING SOMETHING
GO SING SOMETHING TO BUY US TIME
OKAY
THE BOSS MAKES HIS MOVE TOO
It's opening.
What?
"YEOSU NIGHT SEA"
BY BUSKER BUSKER
These vibes are amazing.
Bye!
Bye, 20-year-olds!
The Yeosu night sea
There's a beautiful story
CHECKING THE TIME
Underneath this light
I want to let you hear it
So I call you
You ask what I'm doing
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WE'RE MAKING A CAKE WITH SNACKS
I'm at the Yeosu night sea
What time is it?
Right now?
- It's 11:57 p.m.
- Perfect timing.
- Right on time.
- We should get ready.
This is her gift. It's a vest.
That's great.
ZUHA PREPARED IT IN ADVANCE
- You put this on her.
- Okay.
11:58 P.M.
- He needs to turn off the song now.
- I know.
- He has to turn it off.
- It's time.
LOOK OVER HERE
- Turn it off.
- Hey.
HE DIDN'T SEE THEM
TOTALLY ABSORBED
11:59 P.M.
12:00 A.M.
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu